# **Byounghyun Oh**

[b-young-hyun]

Portfolio ByounghyunOh.com

Contact

HireMe@ByounghyunOh.com

#### **PROFILE**

Currently enrolled in the Computer Programmer course at Confederation College and expected to graduate on June 7, 2019. However, I can begin as work placement student **starting on March 25, 2019** or starting on any time after April 22, 2019 as a full-time employee.

I have been working as the IT Helpdesk Assistant at Confederation College which gave me a variety of software and hardware experiences along with customer experience and critical troubleshooting skills as well.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Computer Peer Tutor - Student IT Helpdesk**

Confederation College | Thunder Bay, Ontario September 2018 - Present

- Technical customer support experience
- Interpersonal communication skill
- Assist another student with computer problems relating to their academic coursework at the College
- Monitoring computer labs to ensure that computer labs are keeping quiet, clean, and secure for everyone

# IT Help Desk Assistant

Confederation College | Thunder Bay, Ontario May 2018 - August 2018

- Critical thinking and logical troubleshooting
- Hands-on experience of PC operating system and network system

- Knowledge of network hardware and server configuration
- Technical customer support experience
- Set up and configure computer workstations in a lab environment
- Refactoring PowerShell Script code and create a new code for automation deployment software images
- Deploy workstation software images using imaging software thoughout academic computer labs, e- classrooms, as well as College staff computers
  - Deployment method: Microsoft System Center Configuration Manager (SCCM) with Pre-boot Execution Environment (PXE)
- Set-up of computer-related equipment to assist with various College summer projects
- Assist College IT staff with network cabling projects
- Assist College IT staff with general e-classroom equipment maintenance projects
- Assist College IT staff with video conference room maintenance/renewal projects
- Provide general end-user IT support and completion of Help Desk trouble tickets

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Confederation College**

Computer Programmer, Diploma | Thunder Bay, Ontario 2017 - 2019 (expected)

#### **Award**

# **Programmer Analyst Excellence Award**

February 2019 | Confederation College

# **SKILLS**

- Languages: C#, SQL, PowerShell, Visual Basic, VBA, Java, Python
- Web: ASP.Net, HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Project Tools: Git, Subversion, Trac, Bugzilla
- Others: Crystal Report, Microsoft Access